The pipe name could not be found. You may\h encounter this error when you reference a pipe\h\h
The pipe name could not be found. 你可能在模板中引用某个管道时遇到此错误
and a template that has either not been imported,\h or not been named properly. Just like components\h\h
它可能没有导入或正确命名
and directives, pipes must be declared or imported\h in an ngModule. In addition, when referenced in a\h\h
就像组件和指令一样，管道也必须在 ngModule 中声明或导入
template, the name must match the name specified\h in the pipe decorator. Angular uses the name in\h\h
另外，当在模板中引用时，此名字必须与管道装饰器中指定的名字相同
a template to determine which pipe to execute.\h That means every pipe must have a name and the\h\h
这意味着每个管道都必须有一个名字，而且
name must be unique to that ngModule. Let's start\h by taking a look at a simple reproduction and\h\h
该名字在所属的 ngModule 中必须是唯一的 让我们看一个简单的错误重现及其解决方案
solution, then we'll review pipes in greater\h detail to understand why this error occurs\h\h
然后，我们会更详细的研究管道，以便理解为何会发生本错误
in our code base. You'll notice we're referencing\h a pipe with the name of truncate, however the red\h\h
你可能注意到我们在使用 truncate 这个名字来引用此管道
underline in VSCode is telling us that Angular\h cannot find a pipe with that name. If you don't\h\h
不过 VSCode 中的红色下划线告诉我们：Angular 无法找到具有这个名字的管道
see the error in VSCode, you might also find it in\h the terminal or in the browser console. In either\h\h
如果你没有在 VSCode 中看到本错误，也会在终端窗口或浏览器控制台中看到
case, the stack trace will direct you to the\h template file that is causing the issue. In order\h\h
无论哪种情况，堆栈跟踪都会为你指出发生此问题的模板
to fix the issue, we'll first want to verify that\h the pipe is available in the appropriate ngModule.\h\h
要想修复本错误，我们先要验证此管道在 ngModule 中是可用的
In this case we're attempting to use the pipe\h in the AppModule. Because it's a custom pipe\h\h
这个例子中，我们试图在 AppModule 中使用此管道
that we're developing in this project, it needs to\h be in the declarations for this Module just like\h\h
因为它是我们正在开发的项目中的自定义管道，所以它需要 像组件或指令一样，声明在此模块中
a component or directive. Now in other cases,\h the pipe may be exported by a different Module\h\h
另一些例子中，管道可能是由其它模块或第三方包导出的
or exported from a third party package, in\h which case you may need to import that Module\h\h
那种情况下，你可能要导入那个模块，而非把那个管道加入 declarations
as opposed to adding the pipe to the declarations.\h At this point we have verified that the pipe is\h\h
这里，我们已经验证过此管道在该 ngModule 中可用
available in the ngModule but we're still getting\h the error. The next piece of code to check is the\h\h
但是仍然有错误。接下来是检查该管道本身的定义
pipe definition itself and specifically the name\h option in the pipe decorator. Notice here how\h\h
特别是 Pipe 装饰器中的 name 选项
the pipe name is 'shorten' but in the template\h it's referenced as 'truncate'. The issue can be\h\h
注意，这里的管道名是 'shorten'，而模板中引用的是 'truncate'
resolved by fixing the mismatch. Either change the\h name referenced in the template or change the name\h\h
只要纠正这个小失误，就可以解决此问题了 既可以修正模板中引用的名字，也可以修改 Pipe 装饰器中的 name
parameter in the pipe decorator. That'll fix the\h issue and it brings up a good opportunity to point\h\h
修复了此问题，我们还要指出一个最佳实践
out a best practice that will prevent issues\h like this from happening in the first place.\h
以防再发生当初那样的错误
When you create a pipe in Angular,\h it's conventional for the pipe name\h\h
当你在 Angular 中创建一个管道时 它会遵循一个约定：管道的名字和定义它的文件名相匹配
to match the file name where it's defined. Notice\h how the pipe name is 'truncate' and the file name\h\h
注意，这里的管道名是 'truncate'，而其文件名是 'truncate.pipe.ts'
is 'truncate.pipe.ts'. When using the Angular CLI,\h this best practice will be applied automatically.\h\h
当使用 Angular CLI 时，会自动应用此最佳实践
Now that we know how to resolve this issue, let's\h do a quick review of how pipes work in Angular to\h\h
现在，我们已经知道如何解决本错误了 让我们在快速过一遍 Angular 中管道的工作原理
understand why this issue happens in the first\h place. The role of a pipe in Angular is to\h\h
以了解当初为什么会发生本错误 在 Angular 中，管道的角色是在模板中对值进行转换
transform values in the template, and unlike\h regular method calls, Angular can optimize\h\h
与常规的方法调用不同，Angular 可以对管道进行优化
pipes. They're especially useful when you have an\h expression or value like a number that needs to be\h\h
当你有一个表达式或值，并且需要把它重新格式化为金额或其它格式时，它会非常有用
or you can create your own from scratch.\h When Angular encounters the pipe character\h\h
而且你也可以创建自己的管道集 当 Angular 在模板表达式中遇到管道符号（|）时
in a template expression, it uses the name of the\h pipe to determine which class has the function to\h\h
它会使用管道名来决定哪个类拥有所要执行的函数
execute. If an invalid name is provided, Angular\h has no way to find the corresponding function,\h\h
如果提供了无效的名字，Angular 就没办法找到对应的函数
but when it is valid it'll match that name\h to the pipe class, which implements a pipe\h\h
而当有效时，它就会根据管道的名字匹配到管道类 该类实现了管道的 transform 函数
transform function. The transform function takes\h the value provided from the template, along with\h\h
这个 transform 函数接受模板中提供的值以及额外参数
any additional arguments, then returns a new\h value which is ultimately shown to the end user.\h\h
然后返回一个新的值，新值会显示给最终用户
Let's go ahead and recap! When you\h encounter the PipeNameNotFoundError,\h\h
我们来回顾一下 当你遇到 PipeNameNotFoundError 时
it means a pipe has been referenced in a\h template that has either not been imported\h\h
它意味着模板中引用的某个管道或者没有导入过
or not been named properly. Resolve\h the issue by first verifying that the\h\h
或者没有被正确命名。 要解决此问题，请先验证此管道已经导入了或者
pipe has been imported or declared in the\h appropriate ngModule. If the issue remains,\h\h
在适当的 ngModule 中声明过
check the pipe definition itself to verify\h that the name matches the name declared in the\h\h
如果问题仍然存在，请检查管道本身的定义， 以验证其名字是否匹配了模板中的名字
template. For additional examples and details,\h reference the official Angular documentation.
欲知详情和范例，请阅读Angular官方文档